C

POOJA JHUNJHUNWALA UI DESIGNER

poojauidesigner@gmail.-



poojauidesigner.-



linkedin.com/in/pooia-



I am a UI designer with a background in pastry art, human development, fashion, and interior design. I was born and raised in India and I have always been passionate about design and creativity. I am experienced in communicating with customers and dedicated to understanding what clients want and need. I empathize with clients and take pride in my organizational skills and attention to detail.

PROJECTS:

- Wagtales- A location-based app created using Balsamiq, Sketch, and Invision for pet parents to find anything pet-related from pet clinics to dog parks or emergency facilities in any area.
- Grocers- An online shopping app designed using Sketch where users can shop their groceries from stores in their area with contact-free delivery.
- Plated Pixiedust- A recipe app created using Sketch, Usability hub, and Invision in which users get a step-by-step recipe and video for Vegetarian and Vegan recipes.
- Ping- A messaging app mini-project created using Sketch and Flinto.
- Remember- A note-taking app mini-project created using Sketch.

EXPERIENCE

Plated Pixiedust- Recipe Developer and Blogger

2019 to now / Website: <u>www.platedpixiedust.com/</u> Platforms: @platedpixiedust

- Design a website using Squarespace and develop recipes for the blog.
- Write and create content- food, and lifestyle blog posts, including editing pictures and videos for each recipe.
- Share the above content on social media platforms such as Instagram, Youtube, Pinterest, and TikTok and analyze data pertaining to posts to create content based on engagement.
- Partner with brands by using their products and giving shareable useful feedback to the community and create shareable content.

Cake by Pooja- Founder and Head Baker

2016 to 2019/ Kolkata, India

Onset Retail store- Intern and Event Managing

SKILLS & TOOLS

Sketch Invision Balsamia Flinto Keynote iMovie **User Flows** Competitor Analysis Wireframing Prototyping **Usability Testing** Style Guides Color schemes Iconography Typography Branding Responsive Design HTML

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry

2020 - 2021

UI Design Program- An intensive project-based course completing many UI/UX projects
Specialization: Front-end Development including Javascript, CSS, and HTML.

Institute of Culinary Education, NYC

2015-2016

Pastry & Baking Diploma Cake Decoration Diploma

JD Birla Institute, Kolkata

2012-2015

BSc in Home Science-Human development, Design, and

LANGUAGE

English, Hindi, Bengali